[{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":20210,"timeElapsed":87261},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":8698,"timeElapsed":95960},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5660,"timeElapsed":101621},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6095,"timeElapsed":107717},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3277,"timeElapsed":110995},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":7522,"timeElapsed":118518},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3649,"timeElapsed":122169},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5704,"timeElapsed":127873},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980809291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2720,"timeElapsed":130594},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6113,"timeElapsed":138169},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980824358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7490,"timeElapsed":145661},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4490,"timeElapsed":150151},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3098,"timeElapsed":153251},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":155985},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7287,"timeElapsed":163273},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2764,"timeElapsed":166038},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980847926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3189,"timeElapsed":169229},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"16","question":"What do you value most in a friendship?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2974,"timeElapsed":172204},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5519,"timeElapsed":179330},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2588,"timeElapsed":181919},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":184831},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":187965},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980869995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3332,"timeElapsed":191298},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3778,"timeElapsed":195077},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3074,"timeElapsed":198152},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3700,"timeElapsed":201853},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980883657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3106,"timeElapsed":204960},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7351,"timeElapsed":213743},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2538,"timeElapsed":216283},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980898286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3306,"timeElapsed":219589},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980900864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":222167},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":224952},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980909321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":5671,"timeElapsed":230624},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980912105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2783,"timeElapsed":233407},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4879,"timeElapsed":238288},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4485,"timeElapsed":242774},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":21350,"timeElapsed":265454},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980946948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":268251},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3262,"timeElapsed":271514},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3686,"timeElapsed":275201},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2251,"timeElapsed":277453},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3106,"timeElapsed":280560},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3675,"timeElapsed":284236},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4129,"timeElapsed":288367},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980969483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2418,"timeElapsed":290786},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5840,"timeElapsed":298009},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980979920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":301223},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6111,"timeElapsed":307335},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3049,"timeElapsed":310385},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5302,"timeElapsed":315688},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":318274},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3158,"timeElapsed":321432},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981002767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2636,"timeElapsed":324070},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3038,"timeElapsed":327109},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7787,"timeElapsed":336079},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2429,"timeElapsed":338509},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981021600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4393,"timeElapsed":342903},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981024308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2707,"timeElapsed":345611},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3754,"timeElapsed":349366},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981033533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5469,"timeElapsed":354836},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":357639},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3201,"timeElapsed":360841},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981042068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2529,"timeElapsed":363371},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981049180,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7111,"timeElapsed":370483},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981058550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":7807,"timeElapsed":379853},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981062563,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4012,"timeElapsed":383866},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981066169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3604,"timeElapsed":387472},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981068949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2780,"timeElapsed":390252},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981072716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3766,"timeElapsed":394019},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981075455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2738,"timeElapsed":396758},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3329,"timeElapsed":400089},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981081803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3017,"timeElapsed":403106},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981085910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4105,"timeElapsed":407213},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981088708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":410011},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981096302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6122,"timeElapsed":417605},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981099951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3648,"timeElapsed":421254},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981103069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3118,"timeElapsed":424372},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981107466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4396,"timeElapsed":428769},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981110073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":431376},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981115953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":5879,"timeElapsed":437256},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981118947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2993,"timeElapsed":440250},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981122216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3268,"timeElapsed":443519},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981125978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"4","question":"What would constitute a perfect day for you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3761,"timeElapsed":447281},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981135012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7098,"timeElapsed":456315},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981137273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2260,"timeElapsed":458576},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981140702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3428,"timeElapsed":462005},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981146340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5637,"timeElapsed":467643},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981149176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":470479},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981152917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3740,"timeElapsed":474220},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981156065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":477368},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3082,"timeElapsed":480451},{"subjectID":"vko479087u","prolificID":"6664f7c85d3674a27eea24b7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b259506a2b9065dd30c2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981162368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3219,"timeElapsed":483671}]